

Samet SunmanFull Stack Developer

🕝 github.com/sametsunman 🚗 A2, B 🛗 09/12/1995 🚳 Single

OBJECTIVE

Hello there, I am 26 years old. Technology have been in my life since I was a kid and I have always loved anything related with computer. I started to code and design at a very young age. Most of my skills and knowledge are self-taugh. I've studied Computer Engineering at Duzce University. During my study I was in Erasmus+ student exchange program at Lublin University of Technology in Poland for one semester. I have successfully completed all my courses and graduated. In the summer of 2017, I did my first internship at Boyner Büyük Mağazacılık A.Ş. in the information technology department as a software intern. In summer of 2018, I completed my second internship at General Mobile's mobile application development unit. I had worked at Ajans Press Group for more than 2 years -since March 2019. I started to work at Yves Rocher Turkey in December 2021. I know C#, Java and Kotlin languages. Also I've expeirence in .NET Core, React and Angular Frameworks.

EDUCATION

(ANADOLU UNIVERSITY

Management Information Systems
Open Education System

UBLIN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Computer Science
Erasmus+ Student Exchange Programme with GPA 3.75

DUZCE UNIVERSITY

Computer Engineering
Obtained the BS degree with GPA 2.86

09/2019 – present Eskisehir, Turkey

09/2018 - 02/2019

Lublin, Poland

09/2013 - 02/2019

Duzce, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

® YVES ROCHER

Mobile Application Developer

- New Mobile Application (React Native, Typescript)
- Old Mobile Application (Ionic, Javascript)
 - · Added new features
 - Performance improvements
 - User interface improvements
 - Published Play Store and App Store
- Backoffice Services (PHP)
 - · Created new api services for mobile applications
 - · Developed api service versions

*¶***AJANS PRESS**

Software Engineer

- Muletools (Asp.NET MVC)
 - · Designed new pages
 - Set CRUD operations
- Medya Bilgi Bankası (React, Javascript)
 - Designed web application
- Backoffice Web (React, Typescript)
 - Designed web application
 - · Created forms, tables
- Backoffice Services (.NET Core)
 - Created Restful API Services
 - Written SQL queries
- Newscope (React, Typescript)
 - Built structure
 - · Created components
 - Entegrated web APIs

GENERAL MOBILE

Mobile Application Development Intern

- Burn Dollars Game (Java, Javascript)
 - Used javascript game engine
 - · Designed game assets
 - Published on Google Play
- Movie Guide App (Kotlin)
 - Developed Application
 - Published on Google Play

BOYNER

Software Development Intern

- Boyner Blog (Html, JavaScript)
 - Developed new modules for Joomla blog based
- Intelligence game (Windows Forms)
 - Created 5 different game level
- Car Race (Asp.NET, Html, JavaScript)
 - Designed game with Html and JavaScript
 - · Converted to multiplayer game using SignalR

11/2021 – present Sişli, İstanbul

03/2019 - 11/2021

Kadıköy, İstanbul

08/2018 - 09/2018 Şişli, İstanbul

08/2017 - 09/2017

Sarıyer, İstanbul



TurkishEnglishPolishNativeB2 - Upper IntermediateA1 - Beginner

COURSES

React Native Bootcamp

Kodluyoruz

11/2020 - 01/2021

Online

High-Level Android Programming with JavaiSMEK

03/2019 - 06/2019
Fatih, istanbul

Web Programming with .Net Core and Multitier Architecture 03/2019 – 06/2019 iSMEK 03/2019 – 06/2019

ORGANISATIONS

Patika Front-End Challenge 04/2021 - 05/2021 Mentor Online

SKILLS

ExperiencesWebsite Development (Backend,Frontend)
Mobile Application
Desktop Application

Frameworks
.NET Core, .NET Framework, ReactJS, VueJS

IDEVisual Studio, Android Studio, Eclipse, Visual
Studio Code

Languages *C#, C++, Java, Kotlin, Go, Javascript, Typescript*

Databases

MsSQL, Oracle Sql, Sqlite, Mongodb, Firebase

Style Libraries & PreprocessorsBootstrap, Material UI, Styled Components, SCSS

Other Technologies

Git, Oop, N-tier Architecture, Entity Framework, LINQ, REST API, Npm, Redux, Axios

INTERESTS

 Movie, Music, Reading, Cycling

REFERENCES

References available on request